(Penny:)How come we can't think
of something we both want to do?
(Amy:)Because you always
pick what we do
(Amy:)and I just
go along with it.
(Leonard:)Ah, interesting--
(Leonard:)we're being accused of
making you do things
(Leonard:)you don't like,
and here you are,
(Leonard:)doing the same
thing to poor Amy.
(Sheldon:)You should point out
the hypocrisy of that.
(Leonard:)That's what I was doing.
(Sheldon:)Oh, that wasn't clear.
(Sheldon:)Try it again, but this time
drive it home
with, "How do you like
them apples, missy?"
(Penny:)All right,
keep thinking.
(Sheldon:)You're making it
too complicated.
(Sheldon:)Why not stick
to the basics?
(Sheldon:)Go shopping for clothes
(Sheldon:)while Leonard and I sit in those
(Sheldon:)uncomfortable chairs
and hold your purses, hmm?
(Sheldon:)I know I'd hate that.
(Sheldon:)Leonard?
(Leonard:)Well, yeah.
(Sheldon:)Well, then, it's settled?
(Amy:)What do you say?
Sounds kind of perfect.
(Penny:)It does-- somehow he managed
(Penny:)to take all the fun out of it.
(Sheldon:)Well, once again,
it's what I do.